let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What does HTML stand for?",
    answer: "C. Hyper Text Markup Language",
    options: [
      "A. Hyper Type Multi Language",
      "B. Hyper Text Multiple Language",
      "C. Hyper Text Markup Language",
      "D. Home Text Multi Language",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What does CSS stand for?",
    answer: "A. Cascading Style Sheet",
    options: [
      "A. Cascading Style Sheet",
      "B. Cute Style Sheet",
      "C. Computer Style Sheet",
      "D. Code Style Sheet",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What does PHP stand for?",
    answer: "A. Hypertext Preprocessor",
    options: [
      "A. Hypertext Preprocessor",
      "B. Hometext Programming",
      "C. Hypertext Preprogramming",
      "D. Programming Hypertext Preprocessor",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What does SQL stand for?",
    answer: "D. Structured Query Language",
    options: [
      "A. Strength Query Language",
      "B. Stylesheet Query Language",
      "C. Science Question Language",
      "D. Structured Query Language",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What does XML stand for?",
    answer: "D. Extensible Markup Language",
    options: [
      "A. Excellent Multiple Language",
      "B. Explore Multiple Language",
      "C. Extra Markup Language",
      "D. Extensible Markup Language",
    ],
  },

  //Additional Questions

  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "The term ‘Computer’ is derived from?",
    answer: "A. Latin",
    options: ["A. Latin", "B. German", "C. French", "D. Arabic"],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Who is the father of Computer?",
    answer: "B. Charles Babbage",
    options: [
      "A. Allen Turing",
      "B. Charles Babbage",
      "C. Simur Cray",
      "D. Augusta Adaming",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The basic operations performed by a computer are?",
    answer: "D. All the above",
    options: [
      "A. Arithmetic operation",
      "B. Logical operation",
      "C. Storage and relative",
      "D. All the above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Who is the father of Internet?",
    answer: "B. Vint Cerf",
    options: [
      "A. Charles Babbage",
      "B. Vint Cerf",
      "C. Denis Riche",
      "D. Martin Cooper",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "If a computer has more than one processor then it is known as?",
    answer: "B. Multiprocessor",
    options: [
      "A. Uni-process",
      "B. Multiprocessor",
      "C. Multi-threaded",
      "D. Multi-programming",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "WWW stands for?",
    answer: "D. World Wide Web",
    options: [
      "A. World Whole Web",
      "B. Wide World Web",
      "C. Web World Wide",
      "D. World Wide Web",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question:
      "A collection of system programs that controls and co-ordinates the overall operations of a computer system is called?",
    answer: "B. Operating system",
    options: [
      "A. System software",
      "B. Operating system",
      "C. Utility program",
      "D. Device driver",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "What type of operating system MS-DOS is?",
    answer: "A. Command Line Interface",
    options: [
      "A. Command Line Interface",
      "B. Graphical User Interface",
      "C. Multitasking",
      "D. Menu Driven Interface",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Which technology is used in compact disks?",
    answer: "D. Laser",
    options: [
      "A. Mechanical",
      "B. Electrical",
      "C. Electro Magnetic",
      "D. Laser",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "1 Gigabyte is equal to?",
    answer: "D. 1024 megabytes",
    options: [
      "A. 1024 bits",
      "B. 1032 megabytes",
      "C. 1024 kilobytes",
      "D. 1024 megabytes",
    ],
  },

  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "The brain of any computer system is?",
    answer: "C. CPU",
    options: ["A. ALU", "B. Memory", "C. CPU", "D. Control unit"],
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question:
      "Which of the following are components of Central Processing Unit (CPU)?",
    answer: "B. Arithmetic logic unit, Control unit",
    options: [
      "A. Arithmetic logic unit, Mouse",
      "B. Arithmetic logic unit, Control unit",
      "C. Arithmetic logic unit, Integrated Circuits",
      "D. Control Unit, Monitor",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "Analog computer works on the supply of?",
    answer: "A. Continuous electrical pulses",
    options: [
      "A. Continuous electrical pulses",
      "B. Electrical pulses but not continuous",
      "C. Magnetic strength",
      "D. None of the above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "Which one is a Digital device, select from the choices below?",
    answer: "A. Digital Clock",
    options: [
      "A. Digital Clock",
      "B. Automobile analog speed meter",
      "C. Clock with a dial and two hands",
      "D. All of them",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "The computer that processes both analog and digital is called?",
    answer: "C. Hybrid computer",
    options: [
      "A. Analog computer",
      "B. Digital computer",
      "C. Hybrid computer",
      "D. Mainframe computer",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 21,
    question: "CD-ROM stands for?",
    answer: "D. Compact Disk Read Only Memory",
    options: [
      "A. Compactable Read Only Memory",
      "B. Compact Data Read Only Memory",
      "C. Compactable Disk Read Only Memory",
      "D. Compact Disk Read Only Memory",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 22,
    question: "ALU is?",
    answer: "A. Arithmetic Logic Unit",
    options: [
      "A. Arithmetic Logic Unit",
      "B. Array Logic Unit",
      "C. Application Logic Unit",
      "D. None of above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 23,
    question: "VGA is?",
    answer: "A. Video Graphics Array",
    options: [
      "A. Video Graphics Array",
      "B. Visual Graphics Array",
      "C. Volatile Graphics Array",
      "D. Video Graphics Adapter",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 24,
    question: "MSI stands for?",
    answer: "A. Medium Scale Integrated Circuits",
    options: [
      "A. Medium Scale Integrated Circuits",
      "B. Medium System Integrated Circuits",
      "C. Medium Scale Intelligent Circuit",
      "D. Medium System Intelligent Circuit",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 25,
    question: "WAN stands for?",
    answer: "B. Wide Area Network",
    options: [
      "A. Wap Area Network",
      "B. Wide Area Network",
      "C. Wide Array Net",
      "D. Wireless Area Network",
    ],
  },

  {
    numb: 26,
    question:
      "What is the main difference between a mainframe and a supercomputer?",
    answer:
      "C. Supercomputers are focused to execute few programs as fast as possible while mainframe uses its power to execute as many programs concurrently",
    options: [
      "A. Supercomputer is much larger than mainframe computers",
      "B. Supercomputers are much smaller than mainframe computers",
      "C. Supercomputers are focused to execute few programs as fast as possible while mainframe uses its power to execute as many programs concurrently",
      "D. Supercomputers are focused to execute as many programs as possible while mainframe uses its power to execute few programs as fast as possible.",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 27,
    question: "Who is called the father of modern digital computer?",
    answer: "A. Allen Turing",
    options: [
      "A. Allen Turing",
      "B. Blaise Pascal",
      "C. Charles Babbage",
      "D. J.H. Muller",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 28,
    question: "Who is the father of Computer science?",
    answer: "A. Allen Turing",
    options: [
      "A. Allen Turing",
      "B. Charles Babbage",
      "C. Simur Cray",
      "D. Augusta Adaming",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 29,
    question: "A CPU contains?",
    answer: "C. a control unit and an arithmetic logic unit",
    options: [
      "A. a card reader and a printing device",
      "B. an analytical engine and a control unit",
      "C. a control unit and an arithmetic logic unit",
      "D. an arithmetic logic unit and a card reader",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 30,
    question:
      "Which of the following controls the process of interaction between the user and the operating system?",
    answer: "A. User interface",
    options: [
      "A. User interface",
      "B. Language translator",
      "C. Platform",
      "D. Screen saver",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 31,
    question: "The first computers were programmed using?",
    answer: "B. Machine language",
    options: [
      "A. Assembly language",
      "B. Machine language",
      "C. Source code",
      "D. Object code",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 32,
    question:
      "What is a combination of hardware and software that facilitates the sharing of information between computing devices?",
    answer: "A. Network",
    options: [
      "A. Network",
      "B. Peripheral",
      "C. Expansion board",
      "D. Digital device",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 33,
    question:
      "Coded entries which are used to gain access to a computer system are called?",
    answer: "B. Passwords",
    options: [
      "A. Entry codes",
      "B. Passwords",
      "C. Security commands",
      "D. Code words",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 34,
    question:
      "Which of the following statements is true about Minicomputer and Microcomputer?",
    answer: "A. Minicomputer works faster than Microcomputer",
    options: [
      "A. Minicomputer works faster than Microcomputer",
      "B. Microcomputer works faster than Minicomputer",
      "C. Speed of both the computers is the same",
      "D. The speeds of both these computers cannot be compared with the speed of advanced",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 35,
    question: "You can organize files by storing them in?",
    answer: "B. Folders",
    options: ["A. Archives", "B. Folders", "C. Indexes", "D. Lists"],
  },

  {
    numb: 36,
    question:
      "What type of resource is most likely to be a shared common resource in a computer network?",
    answer: "A. Printers",
    options: [
      "A. Printers",
      "B. Speakers",
      "C. Floppy disk drives",
      "D. None of these",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 37,
    question: "Which device is required for the Internet connection?",
    answer: "B. Modem",
    options: ["A. Joystick", "B. Modem", "C. CD Drive", "D. NIC Card"],
  },
  {
    numb: 38,
    question: "What is a light pen?",
    answer: "B. Optical input device",
    options: [
      "A. A Mechanical Input device",
      "B. Optical input device",
      "C. Electronic input device",
      "D. Optical output device",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 39,
    question: "UNIVAC is?",
    answer: "A. Universal Automatic Computer",
    options: [
      "A. Universal Automatic Computer",
      "B. Universal Array Computer",
      "C. Unique Automatic Computer",
      "D. Unvalued Automatic Computer",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 40,
    question: "The capacity of a 3.5-inch floppy disk was?",
    answer: "D. 1.44 MB",
    options: ["A. 1.40 MB", "B. 1.44 GB", "C. 1.40 GB", "D. 1.44 MB"],
  },
  {
    numb: 41,
    question: "MICR stands for?",
    answer: "A. Magnetic Ink Character Recognition",
    options: [
      "A. Magnetic Ink Character Recognition",
      "B. Magnetic Ink Code Reader",
      "C. Magnetic Ink Cases Reader",
      "D. None of these",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 42,
    question: "EBCDIC stands for?",
    answer: "A. Extended Binary Coded Decimal Interchange Code",
    options: [
      "A. Extended Binary Coded Decimal Interchange Code",
      "B. Extended Bit Code Decimal Interchange Code",
      "C. Extended Bit Case Decimal Interchange Code",
      "D. Extended Binary Case Decimal Interchange Code",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 43,
    question:
      "Which of the following is a part of the Central Processing Unit?",
    answer: "D. Arithmetic & Logic unit",
    options: [
      "A. Printer",
      "B. Keyboard",
      "C. Mouse",
      "D. Arithmetic & Logic unit",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 44,
    question: "CAD stands for?",
    answer: "A. Computer Aided Design",
    options: [
      "A. Computer Aided Design",
      "B. Computer Algorithm for Design",
      "C. Computer Application in Design",
      "D. Computer Analogue Design",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 45,
    question: "Junk e-mail is also called?",
    answer: "A. Spam",
    options: ["A. Spam", "B. Spoof", "C. Sniffer Script", "D. Spool"],
  },

  {
    numb: 46,
    question: "Which statement describes 'Hackers'?",
    answer: "B. Break into other people’s computers",
    options: [
      "A. All have the same motive",
      "B. Break into other people’s computers",
      "C. May legally break into computers as long as they do not do any damage",
      "D. Are people who are allergic to computers",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 47,
    question:
      "What type of computers are client computers (most of the time) in a client-server system?",
    answer: "C. Microcomputer",
    options: ["A. Mainframe", "B. Mini-computer", "C. Microcomputer", "D. PDA"],
  },
  {
    numb: 48,
    question: "A computer cannot 'boot' if it does not have the?",
    answer: "C. Operating System",
    options: [
      "A. Compiler",
      "B. Loader",
      "C. Operating System",
      "D. Assembler",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 49,
    question:
      "The amount of vertical space between lines of text in a document is called?",
    answer: "B. Line spacing",
    options: [
      "A. Double-space",
      "B. Line spacing",
      "C. Single space",
      "D. Vertical spacing",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 50,
    question: "Example of non-numeric data is?",
    answer: "A. Employee address",
    options: [
      "A. Employee address",
      "B. Examination score",
      "C. Bank balance",
      "D. All of these",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 51,
    question: "What is an embedded system?",
    answer: "C. The computer which is part of a larger system or machine",
    options: [
      "A. The program which arrives by being wrapped in a box.",
      "B. The program which is the permanent part of the computer.",
      "C. The computer which is part of a larger system or machine",
      "D. The computer and software system that control the machine",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 52,
    question: "When a file is saved for the first time?",
    answer: "B. It must be given a name to identify it",
    options: [
      "A. A copy is automatically printed",
      "B. It must be given a name to identify it",
      "C. It does not need a name",
      "D. It only needs a name if it is not going to be printed",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 53,
    question: "Where are data and program stored when the processor uses them?",
    answer: "A. Main memory",
    options: [
      "A. Main memory",
      "B. Secondary memory",
      "C. Disk memory",
      "D. Program memory",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 54,
    question: "___represents raw facts, whereas___is data made meaningful?",
    answer: "B. Data, information",
    options: [
      "A. Information, reporting",
      "B. Data, information",
      "C. Information, bits",
      "D. Records, bytes",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 55,
    question: "What characteristic of read-only memory (ROM) makes it useful?",
    answer:
      "B. Data in ROM is non-volatile, that is, it remains there even without electrical power.",
    options: [
      "A. ROM information can be easily updated.",
      "B. Data in ROM is non-volatile, that is, it remains there even without electrical power.",
      "C. ROM provides very large amounts of inexpensive data storage.",
      "D. ROM chips are easily swapped between different brands of computers.",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 56,
    question:
      "What do you call the programs that are used to find out possible faults and their causes?",
    answer: "C. Diagnostic software",
    options: [
      "A. Operating system extensions",
      "B. Cookies",
      "C. Diagnostic software",
      "D. Boot diskettes",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 57,
    question:
      "Which programming languages are classified as low-level languages?",
    answer: "D. Assembly languages",
    options: [
      "A. BASIC, COBOL, Fortran",
      "B. Prolog",
      "C. C, C++",
      "D. Assembly languages",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 58,
    question: "Which of the following is not antivirus software?",
    answer: "C. Oracle",
    options: ["A. Avira", "B. Kaspersky", "C. Oracle", "D. McAfee"],
  },
  {
    numb: 59,
    question: "What does DMA stand for?",
    answer: "B. Direct Memory Access",
    options: [
      "A. Distinct Memory Access",
      "B. Direct Memory Access",
      "C. Direct Module Access",
      "D. Direct Memory Allocation",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 60,
    question: "Which of the following is a storage device?",
    answer: "D. All of the above",
    options: [
      "A. Tape",
      "B. Hard Disk",
      "C. Floppy Disk",
      "D. All of the above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 61,
    question: "When did John Napier develop logarithms?",
    answer: "B. 1614",
    options: ["A. 1416", "B. 1614", "C. 1641", "D. 1804"],
  },
  {
    numb: 62,
    question:
      "MIS is designed to provide information needed for effective decision making by?",
    answer: "D. Managers",
    options: ["A. Consumers", "B. Workers", "C. Foremen", "D. Managers"],
  },
  {
    numb: 63,
    question: "ASCII stands for__________?",
    answer: "C. American Standard Code for Information Interchange",
    options: [
      "A. American Stable Code for International Interchange",
      "B. American Standard Case for Institutional Interchange",
      "C. American Standard Code for Information Interchange",
      "D. American Standard Code for Interchange Information",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 64,
    question: "Which of the following is the first generation of computer?",
    answer: "A. EDSAC",
    options: ["A. EDSAC", "B. IBM-1401", "C. CDC-1604", "D. ICL-2900"],
  },
  {
    numb: 65,
    question: "IBM 1401 is_________?",
    answer: "B. Second Generation Computer",
    options: [
      "A. First Generation Computer",
      "B. Second Generation Computer",
      "C. Third Generation Computer",
      "D. Fourth Generation Computer",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 66,
    question: "Chief component of the first-generation computer was____?",
    answer: "B. Vacuum Tubes and Valves",
    options: [
      "A. Transistors",
      "B. Vacuum Tubes and Valves",
      "C. Integrated Circuits",
      "D. None of the above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 67,
    question: "Second Generation computers were developed during____?",
    answer: "B. 1956 to 1965",
    options: [
      "A. 1949 to 1955",
      "B. 1956 to 1965",
      "C. 1965 to 1970",
      "D. 1970 to 1990",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 68,
    question: "The computer size was very large in____?",
    answer: "A. First Generation",
    options: [
      "A. First Generation",
      "B. Second Generation",
      "C. Third Generation",
      "D. Fourth Generation",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 69,
    question:
      "Microprocessors as switching devices are for ___ generation computers?",
    answer: "D. Fourth Generation",
    options: [
      "A. First Generation",
      "B. Second Generation",
      "C. Third Generation",
      "D. Fourth Generation",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 70,
    question:
      "Which of the following devices can be used to directly image printed text?",
    answer: "A. OCR",
    options: ["A. OCR", "B. OMR", "C. MICR", "D. All of the above"],
  },
  {
    numb: 71,
    question: "The output quality of a printer is measured by____?",
    answer: "A. Dot per inch",
    options: [
      "A. Dot per inch",
      "B. Dot per sq. inch",
      "C. Dots printed per unit time",
      "D. All of above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 72,
    question: "In an analogue computer_______?",
    answer: "B. Input is never converted to digital form",
    options: [
      "A. Input is first converted to digital form",
      "B. Input is never converted to digital form",
      "C. Output is displayed in digital form",
      "D. All of above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 73,
    question:
      "In the latest generation computers, the instructions are executed_____?",
    answer: "C. Both sequentially and parallel",
    options: [
      "A. Parallel only",
      "B. Sequentially only",
      "C. Both sequentially and parallel",
      "D. All of above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 74,
    question: "Who designed the first electronic computer – ENIAC?",
    answer: "C. J. Presper Eckert and John W Mauchly",
    options: [
      "A. Van-Neumann",
      "B. Joseph M. Jacquard",
      "C. J. Presper Eckert and John W Mauchly",
      "D. All of above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 75,
    question: "Who invented the high-level language 'C'?",
    answer: "A. Dennis M. Ritchie",
    options: [
      "A. Dennis M. Ritchie",
      "B. Niklaus Writh",
      "C. Seymour Papert",
      "D. Donald Kunth",
    ],
  },

  {
    numb: 76,
    question:
      "Personnel who design, program, operate, and maintain computer equipment refers to____?",
    answer: "C. Peopleware",
    options: [
      "A. Console-operator",
      "B. Programmer",
      "C. Peopleware",
      "D. System Analyst",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 77,
    question:
      "An error in software or hardware is called a bug. What is the alternative computer jargon for it?",
    answer: "D. Glitch",
    options: ["A. Leech", "B. Squid", "C. Slug", "D. Glitch"],
  },
  {
    numb: 78,
    question: "Modern computers are very reliable, but they are not___?",
    answer: "C. Infallible",
    options: ["A. Fast", "B. Powerful", "C. Infallible", "D. Cheap"],
  },
  {
    numb: 79,
    question:
      "Personal computers use a number of chips mounted on a main circuit board. What is the common name for such boards?",
    answer: "B. Motherboard",
    options: [
      "A. Daughter board",
      "B. Motherboard",
      "C. Father board",
      "D. Breadboard",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 80,
    question: "What is meant by a dedicated computer?",
    answer: "B. Which is assigned one and only one task",
    options: [
      "A. Which is used by one person only",
      "B. Which is assigned one and only one task",
      "C. Which uses one kind of software",
      "D. Which is meant for application software",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 81,
    question:
      "The system unit of a personal computer typically contains all of the following except:",
    answer: "D. Modem",
    options: [
      "A. Microprocessor",
      "B. Disk controller",
      "C. Serial interface",
      "D. Modem",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 82,
    question:
      "A computer program that converts an entire program into machine language is called a/an",
    answer: "C. Compiler",
    options: ["A. Interpreter", "B. Simulator", "C. Compiler", "D. Commander"],
  },
  {
    numb: 83,
    question:
      "A small or intelligent device is so called because it contains within it a?",
    answer: "D. Sensor",
    options: [
      "A. Computer",
      "B. Microcomputer",
      "C. Programmable",
      "D. Sensor",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 84,
    question:
      "A fault in a computer program that prevents it from working correctly is known as?",
    answer: "B. Bug",
    options: ["A. Boot", "B. Bug", "C. Biff", "D. Strap"],
  },
  {
    numb: 85,
    question:
      "A self-replicating program, similar to a virus which was taken from a 1970s science fiction novel by John Bruner entitled the Shockwave Rider is?",
    answer: "D. Worm",
    options: ["A. Bug", "B. Vice", "C. Lice", "D. Worm"],
  },
  {
    numb: 86,
    question:
      "Unwanted repetitious messages, such as unsolicited bulk e-mail is known as?",
    answer: "A. Spam",
    options: ["A. Spam", "B. Trash", "C. Calibri", "D. Courier"],
  },
  {
    numb: 87,
    question: "DOS stands for?",
    answer: "A. Disk Operating System",
    options: [
      "A. Disk Operating System",
      "B. Disk operating session",
      "C. Digital Operating System",
      "D. Digital Open system",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 88,
    question: "Who is the Current CEO of Microsoft?",
    answer: "D. Satya Nadella",
    options: [
      "A. Babbage",
      "B. Bill Gates",
      "C. Bill Clinton",
      "D. Satya Nadella",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 89,
    question: "Which of the following are input devices?",
    answer: "D. All of these",
    options: ["A. Keyboard", "B. Mouse", "C. Card reader", "D. All of these"],
  },
  {
    numb: 90,
    question: "Examples of output devices are?",
    answer: "D. All of these",
    options: ["A. Screen", "B. Printer", "C. Speaker", "D. All of these"],
  },
  {
    numb: 91,
    question:
      "Which of the following is also known as the brain of the computer?",
    answer: "B. Central Processing Unit",
    options: [
      "A. Control unit",
      "B. Central Processing Unit",
      "C. Arithmetic and language unit",
      "D. Monitor",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 92,
    question:
      "____ translates and executes the program at runtime line by line?",
    answer: "B. Interpreter",
    options: ["A. Compiler", "B. Interpreter", "C. Linker", "D. Loader"],
  },
  {
    numb: 93,
    question: "RAM stands for_____?",
    answer: "D. Random access memory",
    options: [
      "A. Random origin money",
      "B. Random only memory",
      "C. Read-only memory",
      "D. Random access memory",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 94,
    question: "1 Byte =____?",
    answer: "A. 8 bits",
    options: ["A. 8 bits", "B. 4 bits", "C. 2 bits", "D. 9 bits"],
  },
  {
    numb: 95,
    question: "BIOS stands for_____?",
    answer: "A. Basic Input Output system",
    options: [
      "A. Basic Input Output system",
      "B. Binary Input output system",
      "C. Basic Input Off system",
      "D. All of the above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 96,
    question: "Father of 'C‘ programming language?",
    answer: "A. Dennis Ritchie",
    options: [
      "A. Dennis Ritchie",
      "B. Prof John Keenly",
      "C. Thomas Kurtz",
      "D. Bill Gates",
    ],
  },

  {
    numb: 97,
    question:
      "The instructions that tell a computer how to carry out the processing tasks are referred to as computer?",
    answer: "A. Programs",
    options: [
      "A. Programs",
      "B. Processors",
      "C. Input devices",
      "D. Memory modules",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 98,
    question:
      "An area of a computer that temporarily holds data waiting to be processed is?",
    answer: "B. Memory",
    options: ["A. CPU", "B. Memory", "C. Storage", "D. File"],
  },
  {
    numb: 99,
    question:
      "___ is the key to close a selected drop-down list; cancel a command and close a dialog box.",
    answer: "C. ESC",
    options: ["A. TAB", "B. SHIFT", "C. ESC", "D. F10"],
  },
  {
    numb: 100,
    question: "____ is the key we use to run the selected command?",
    answer: "C. ENTER",
    options: ["A. SHIFT", "B. TAB", "C. ENTER", "D. CTRL"],
  },
  {
    numb: 101,
    question: "_____ is the functional key to display the save-as box?",
    answer: "D. F12",
    options: ["A. F5", "B. F6", "C. F9", "D. F12"],
  },
  {
    numb: 102,
    question:
      "Data becomes_____ when it is presented in a format that people can understand and use.",
    answer: "C. Information",
    options: ["A. Processed", "B. Graphs", "C. Information", "D. Presentation"],
  },
  {
    numb: 103,
    question:
      "The term_____ designates equipment that might be added to a computer system to enhance its functionality.",
    answer: "D. Peripheral Device",
    options: [
      "A. Digital device",
      "B. System add-on",
      "C. Disk pack",
      "D. Peripheral device",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 104,
    question: "A ______ is a microprocessor-based computing device?",
    answer: "A. Personal computer",
    options: [
      "A. Personal computer",
      "B. Mainframe",
      "C. Workstation",
      "D. Server",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 105,
    question: "RAM can be treated as the_____ for the computer’s processor?",
    answer: "C. Waiting room",
    options: [
      "A. Factory",
      "B. Operating room",
      "C. Waiting room",
      "D. Planning room",
    ],
  },
];
